FELIX E MIRANDA T

Full-Stack Developer

Portfolio - www.mirandadeveloper.com

Well-qualified Frontend Developer familiar with the main programming utilities and languages. Knowledge of backend and frontend development requirements. Able to handle any part of the process with efficiency and best practices. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 2+ years of related experience.

Work History

2019-07current

Full Stack Developer

Freelancer, Bogotá, Colombia

 Developed aplications and pages for local businesses using too Is such as JavaScript, React Js, NextJs, NodeJs, Material UI, Bootstrap, MongoDB, PostgreSQL with Prisma and FastAPI with Python

2016-12 -2018-06

Web Builder

Easy Software SAS, Bogotá, Colombia

Education

2013 - 06

Technologist in Customs Management and Foreign Trade

Universidad Jorge Tadeo Lozano - Colombia

1999 - 12

Courses

High School Diploma

Colegio Americano - Barranguilla - Colombia

Next JS React Framework, Udemy (2021)

Contact

Address

Calle 12A # 71b -61 Bogotá D.C, 110831

Phone

57-350-7107300

E-mail

feedmite@hotmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.co m /in/fmirandat/

Skills

HTML **CSS**

Bootstrap MaterialUI

JavaScript React.js

Node.js

Next.js

PostgreSQL with Prisma

Python

Languages

Spanish



English



 React Js, Udemy (2020) · React Js, Documentation

B₂